A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Office of the President, Senior Advisor, Office Files of Frank DeGiovanni FA1876
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subject files, 1990-2016; 2; 26.91 Cubic Feet 67.5 document boxes: 53.5 letter boxes and 14 legal boxes
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED), 2005 (Box 32, Folder 440)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) Universal Model - 529 savings plans, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 441)
  - National Federation of Community Development Credit Unions (NFCDCU) proposal, 2009 (Box 32, Folder 442)
  - Affinity Group on Development Finance (AGDF) 15 Annual Meeting, November 2008, New York City, New York (Box 32, Folder 443)
  - Living Cities Capital Formation Committee October 2009 Meeting (Box 32, Folder 444)
  - Central Appalachia community economic development, 2009 (Box 32, Folder 445)
  - BRAC Africa Loan Fund, 2008 (Box 32, Folder 446)
  - Fiscal Year 2008 presentations and reports (Box 32, Folder 447-448)
  - Ford Foundation Savings and Asset Building grantmaking assessment, 2008 (Box 33, Folder 449)
  - Social Performance Task Force (SPTF) bylaws and other materials, 2009 (Box 33, Folder 450)
  - Ford Foundation job descriptions, undated (Box 33, Folder 451)
  - Office of Financial Empowerment (OFE) SaveNYC proposal, 2009 (Box 33, Folder 452)
  - ShoreBank, 2008-2009 (Box 33, Folder 453)
  - Lagos, Nigeria Regional Office Financial Assets unit Program Officer applicants, 2009 (Box 33, Folder 454)
  - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) Program Officer applicants, 2005-2009 (Box 33, Folder 455-456)
  - Fiscal Year 2009 working file - Economic development and assets programming, part 1, 2006-2009 (Box 33, Folder 457-458)
  - Fiscal Year 2009 working file - Economic development and assets programming, part 2 (Box 34, Folder 459)
  - Program Related Investments (PRI) 2003 internal audit (Box 34, Folder 460)
  - Program Related Investments (PRI) loss reserve adjustment, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 461)
  - Program Related Investments (PRI) portfolio meeting, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 462)
  - University of North Carolina Center for Community Capital (CCC) - Community Advantage Panel Survey (CAPS) in-person vs. phone responses, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 463)
  - Lower Income Households and the Automobile Insurance Marketplace Ford Foundation September 2011 Grantees Convening (Box 34, Folder 464)
  - Program Related Investments (PRI) 2009 internal audit (Box 34, Folder 465)
  - Fiscal Year 2010 meeting budget, 2009-2010 (Box 34, Folder 466)
  - Program Related Investments (PRI) summary process, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 467)
  - Center Appalachian Network (CAN)/Appalachia Funders Network August 2011 Meeting, Lewisburg, West Virginia (Box 34, Folder 468)
  - Enterprise Cleveland Group (ECG), 2011 (Box 34, Folder 469)
  - Global Impact Investing Network (GIIN) Terragua Member Study, undated (Box 34, Folder 470)
  - The Progress Fund, undated (Box 34, Folder 471)
  - Buffalo Ridge Safari Lodge 2008-2009 financials projections (Box 34, Folder 472)
  - Fiscal Year 2008 miscellaneous reports (Box 34, Folder 473)
  - BRAC, 1994-2008 (Box 34, Folder 474)
  - Luis Ubinas speech - Notes, undated (Box 34, Folder 475)
  - Stabilization Trust REO Capital Fund, 2008-2009 (Box 34, Folder 476)
  - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) Economic Development unit Program Officer Reflection Memos, 2007 (Box 34, Folder 477)
  - Expanding Livelihood Opportunities for Poor Household Initiatives (ELOPHI) February 2008 presentation (Box 34, Folder 478)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) miscellaneous materials, 2005-2009 (Box 34, Folder 479)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) - Fiscal Year 2005 final budgets, 2004-2005 (Box 35, Folder 480)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) cost projections, 2006-2007 (Box 35, Folder 481)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) for Oklahoma Kids - Research Triangle Institute (RTI) survey, 2007 (Box 35, Folder 482)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) - 2009-2010 grant period, 2008-2009 (Box 35, Folder 483)
  - Saving for Education. Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) Universal Model, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 484)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) Research Advisory Council October 2006 Meeting (Box 35, Folder 485)
  - Access Exchange International newsletter, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 486)
  - AGREE Advisory Committee, 2011-2012 (Box 35, Folder 487)
  - Asociacion Nacional De Empresas Comercializadoras de Productores del Campo (ANEC) (National Association of Small Producers Organizations), 2011 (Box 35, Folder 488)
  - Assets and the Poor at 21, undated (Box 35, Folder 489)
  - BASIX, 2011-2013 (Box 35, Folder 490)
  - Building Economic Security Over a Lifetime (BESOL), 2011-2013 (Box 35, Folder 491)
  - Monitoring and Evaluation - Building Economic Security Over a Lifetime (BESOL) and Financial Products and Services (FPS), 2012 (Box 35, Folder 492)
  - Building Economic Security Over a Lifetime (BESOL) Initiative Status Summary, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 493)
  - Building Economic Security Over a Lifetime (BESOL) Initiative Status Summary, 2013 (Box 36, Folder 494)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit 2011 biennium budget (Box 36, Folder 495)
  - Better Than Cash Alliance (BTCA), 2012-2013 (Box 36, Folder 496)
  - Better Than Cash Alliance (BTCA), 2013 (Box 36, Folder 497)
  - Carsey Institute - Assessing the Impacts of Federal Farm Bill Programs on Rural Communities, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 498)
  - Center for Global Development (CGD), 2011-2012 (Box 36, Folder 499)
  - Microfinance CEOs Working Group - Social Performance Task Force (SPTF) universal standards for social performance management, 2011 (Box 36, Folder 500)
  - Corporation for Enterprise Development (CFED), 2012 (Box 36, Folder 501)
  - Center for Financial Services Innovation (CFSI), 2011 (Box 36, Folder 502)
  - Center for Financial Services Innovation (CFSI), 2010-2011 (Box 36, Folder 503)
  - Center for Financial Services Innovation (CFSI) Underbanked Industry Scan, 2011 (Box 36, Folder 504)
  - Consultative Group to Assist the Poor (CGAP) – G2P (government to person) program, 2011-2012 (Box 36, Folder 505)
  - August 2012 Colombia trip (Box 36, Folder 506)
  - Centre for Social Protection (CSP) – Graduation in social protection programs, 2011 (Box 36, Folder 507)
  - Economic Policy Research Institute (EPRI) - Savings accounts and child support grant, 2011 (Box 36, Folder 508)
  - Economic Opportunities for Rural Poor Mexico and Central America Program Officer candidates, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 509)
  - EDA Rural Systems - India social performance reporting, 2011 (Box 36, Folder 510)
  - Expanding Livelihood Opportunities for Poor Households Initiative (ELOPHI) Fiscal Year 2012, 2011-2012 (Box 36, Folder 511)
  - Expanding Livelihood Opportunities for Poor Households Initiative (ELOPHI) Initiative Status Summary, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 512)
  - Expanding Livelihood Opportunities for Poor Households Initiative (ELOPHI) measurement and evaluation, 2012-2013 (Box 37, Folder 513)
  - January 2012 Peru trip, 2011-2012 (Box 37, Folder 514)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit September 2011 meeting with Pablo Farias (Box 37, Folder 515)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit July 2011 presentation to Luis Ubinas (Box 37, Folder 516)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit Fiscal Year 2012 grantmaking plan narrative, 2011 (Box 37, Folder 517)
  - Ford Foundation programs and initiatives outline, 2011 (Box 37, Folder 518)
  - FOC, 2011 (Box 37, Folder 519)
  - Improving Access to Financial Services Initiative - Initiative status, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 520)
  - Improving Access to Financial Services Initiative - Theory of Change, 2011 (Box 37, Folder 521)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit Fiscal Year 2012 biennium budget, 2011 (Box 37, Folder 522)
  - Fiscal Year 2012 – Theory of Change, circa 2011-2012 (Box 37, Folder 523)
  - Graduation program qualitative study, 2011-2012 (Box 37, Folder 524)
  - 2012 grants to discuss with Anil Oommen (Box 37, Folder 525)
  - Hattaway Communications - Asset Building Programs Focus Groups Phase 2, 2010-2011 (Box 37, Folder 526)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Program Retreat, 2011 (Box 37, Folder 527)
  - Program Related Investments (PRI) December 2013 Year-End Loss Reserve Meeting (Box 37, Folder 528)
  - 2012-2013 meeting materials and notes, 2007-2013 (Box 38, Folder 529-530)
  - 2012-2013 meeting materials and notes, part 1, 2010-2013 (Box 38, Folder 531-533)
  - 2012-2013 meeting materials and notes, part 2, 2011-2013 (Box 39, Folder 534)
  - 2012-2013 meeting materials and notes, 2002-2013 (Box 39, Folder 535-537)
  - Value chain proposals, 2011 (Box 39, Folder 538)
  - Sustainable Food Lab (SFL) - Value chains and the poor, 2011 (Box 39, Folder 539)
  - Self-Help United States mortgage statistics, undated (Box 39, Folder 540)
  - Targeting the Ultra Poor (TUP) pilot program in Lempira, Honduras, 2009 (Box 39, Folder 541)
  - Comments on Program Related Investment (PRI) - Extreme poverty line, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 542)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit October 2010 presentation to Luis Ubinas - Overview of Program Strategy (Box 39, Folder 543)
  - Building Economic Security Over a Lifetime (BESOL) Theory of Change, 2011 (Box 39, Folder 544)
  - National Academy of Social Insurance (NASI) subgrant proposals, 2009-2010 (Box 39, Folder 545)
  - Self-Help Ventures Fund Program Related Investment (PRI), 2000-2009 (Box 40, Folder 546)
  - 2002-2003 reports and meeting materials, 2002-2004 (Box 40, Folder 547-550)
  - Affinity Group on Development Finance (AGDF) September-October 2003 Annual Meeting, Portland, Maine, 2002-2011 (Box 41, Folder 551)
  - ISEAL Alliance October 2011 project launch meeting, Bonn, Germany, 1999-2011 (Box 41, Folder 552)
  - ISEAL Alliance June 2011 Conference, Zurich, Switzerland (Box 41, Folder 553)
  - ISEAL Alliance October 2011 project launch meeting, Bonn, Germany (Box 41, Folder 554)
  - Expanding Livelihood Opportunities for Poor Households Initiative (ELOPHI) April 2011 Program Officers Meeting, London, United Kingdom - Pattern analysis (Box 41, Folder 555)
  - Expanding Livelihood Opportunities for Poor Households Initiative (ELOPHI) April 2011 Program Officers Meeting, London, England - Impact and survey, 2008-2011 (Box 41, Folder 556)
  - Expanding Livelihood Opportunities for Poor Households Initiative (ELOPHI) April 2011 Program Officers Meeting, London, England - Inclusive Business Workshop (Box 41, Folder 557)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit initiative budget narratives, 2011 (Box 41, Folder 558)
  - Reports and meeting materials - Value chains, pro-poor development, and livelihoods, 2008-2010 (Box 41, Folder 559)
  - Livelihood Learning Group, 2011 (Box 41, Folder 560)
  - 2005 Affinity Group on Development Finance (AGDF) (Box 41, Folder 561)
  - Consultative Group to Assist the Poor (CGAP) November 2005 Meeting, Oaxaca, Mexico - Readings, 2004-2005 (Box 41, Folder 562-563)
  - International Livestock Research Institute (ILRI) papers on livelihoods, 2011 (Box 42, Folder 564)
  - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) May 2005 livelihood presentations to Board of Trustees (Box 42, Folder 565)
  - October 2009 Costa Rica trip - Tropical Agricultural Research and Higher Education Center (CATIE), 2007-2009 (Box 42, Folder 566)
  - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) - Reports and meeting materials, 2001-2004 (Box 42, Folder 567-570)
  - Miscellaneous reports and meeting materials, 2001-2015; File contains digital media (Box 43, Folder 571-573)
  - Conversation on Coverage - Working Group Minutes, undated (Box 43, Folder 572)
  - Corporation for Enterprise Development (CFED) Assets and Opportunity Scorecard, 2009-2011 (Box 43, Folder 574)
  - Asset Framework - Kilolo Kijakazi, 2004-2005 (Box 43, Folder 575)
  - New Ownership Society, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 576)
  - BASIX, 1996-2003 (Box 43, Folder 577)
  - University of North Carolina Center for Community Capitalism (CCC) - Community Advantage Panel (CAP) panel attrition, 2006-2011 (Box 43, Folder 578)
  - University of North Carolina Center for Community Capitalism (CCC) - Ford Foundation Trustees 2007 presentation (Box 44, Folder 579)
  - Ford Foundation May 2006 Program Retreat (Box 44, Folder 580)
  - Department for International Development (DFID) MICFAC Africa (Microfinance Capacity Building Facility for Sub-Saharan Africa), 2009-2010 (Box 44, Folder 581)
  - May 2010 Kenya trip - Consultative Group to Assist the Poor (CGAP) (Box 44, Folder 582)
  - Center For Family Policy and Practice (CFFPP), 2009-2010 (Box 44, Folder 583)
  - Kenya Women Finance Trust (KWFT), 2010-2011 (Box 44, Folder 584)
  - Sustainability Standards Movement, 2009-2011 (Box 44, Folder 585)
  - Aspen Institute Initiative on Financial Security - Social security paper, 2011 (Box 44, Folder 586)
  - Conditional cash transfer conference, November 2011, circa 2011 (Box 44, Folder 587)
  - December 2010 Rio Grande Valley site visit (Box 44, Folder 588)
  - Self Help California notes, 2010 (Box 44, Folder 589)
  - Building Economic Security Over a Lifetime (BESOL) Theory of Change, undated (Box 44, Folder 590)
  - Endowment report - Corporation for Enterprise Development (CFED), 2010-2011 (Box 44, Folder 591)
  - Asset building - Reports and presentations, part 1, 2000-2011 (Box 44, Folder 592-594)
  - Asset building - Reports and presentations, part 2, 2003-2005 (Box 45, Folder 595)
  - University of North Carolina Center for Community Capital (CCC) - Self-Help Ventures Fund, 1998-2011 (Box 45, Folder 596-597)
  - Sustainable Food Lab (SFL) June 2011 Leadership Summit, Portland, Oregon, 2008-2011; File contains digital media (Box 45, Folder 598)
  - After the Harvest: Fighting Hunger in the Coffeelands, undated (Box 45, Folder 598)
  - Program Related Investments (PRI) automation responsibilities, 2006 (Box 45, Folder 599)
  - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) Economic Development unit Program Related Investments (PRI) - Internal audit, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 600)
  - Living Cities, 2008-2011 (Box 45, Folder 601)
  - Financial Services - Theory of Change, 2011 (Box 45, Folder 602)
  - Sustainable Food Lab (SFL)/ISEAL Alliance - Value chains, 2010 (Box 45, Folder 603)
  - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) Economic Development unit, 2007-2008 (Box 45, Folder 604)
  - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) Economic Development unit meetings, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 605)
  - Expanding Livelihood Opportunities to Poor Households Initiative (ELOPHI) Learning Group Meeting, October 2009 Turrialba, Costa Rica (Box 46, Folder 606)
  - Ford Foundation Directors' June 2008 Retreat - Line of Work Statements (Box 46, Folder 607)
  - March 2008 Chile and Peru (Box 46, Folder 608)
  - Americans for Financial Reform (AFR) policy papers list, 2010 (Box 46, Folder 609)
  - Self-Help California Expansion Opportunity, 2011 (Box 46, Folder 610)
  - Earth Institute, 2011 (Box 46, Folder 611)
  - Research Triangle Institute (RTI) - Universal Model sampling issues, 2006-2007 (Box 46, Folder 612)
  - Urban Institute proposal - New Unemployment, 2010 (Box 46, Folder 613)
  - Wealth Creation in Rural Communities, 2010 (Box 46, Folder 614)
  - Asset building and microfinance - Meeting materials, reports, and proposals, part 1, 2001-2003 (Box 46, Folder 615-616)
  - Asset building and microfinance - Meeting materials, reports, and proposals, part 2, 2002-2010 (Box 47, Folder 617-619)
  - Affinity Group on Development Finance (AGDF) November 2005 Annual Meeting, Tzaneen, South Africa, File contains one still image (Box 47, Folder 620-621)
    File contains a photograph. The photograph is a group picture from the Affinity Group on Development Finance (AGDF) 2005 Annual Meeting in Tzaneen, South Africa.
  - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) Economic Development unit regional programming - Memos and grant action records, 2003-2005 (Box 47, Folder 622)
  - August 2007 China visit (Box 47, Folder 623)
  - Ajit Kanitkar Program Officer Memo feedback, 2007 (Box 47, Folder 624)
  - Aspen Institute Business and Society Program, 2006 (Box 48, Folder 625)
  - Detroit funding, 2006 (Box 48, Folder 626)
  - Consultative Group to Assist the Poor (CGAP) September 2009 Executive Committee Meeting, Washington D.C., 2006-2009 (Box 48, Folder 627)
  - Consultative Group to Assist the Poor (CGAP)-Ford Foundation Trickle Up (TUP) Graduation Project, 2006 (Box 48, Folder 628)
  - Aspen Institute Initiative on Financial Security November 2005 Meeting (Box 48, Folder 629)
  - Analysis of Program Officer Memos, 2006-2009 (Box 48, Folder 630)
  - Doorways to Dreams Fund (D2D) 2009 Update (Box 48, Folder 631)
  - Consumer Financial Protection Bureau (CFPB) reports, 2011 (Box 48, Folder 632)
  - Alliance for a Green Revolution in Africa (AGRA) - Investment Fund for African Agriculture (IIFFAA), 2011 (Box 48, Folder 633)
  - Shared Interest - South Africa, 2010-2011 (Box 48, Folder 634)
  - Economic Opportunity and Asserts Program (EOA) - Improving Access to Financial Services theory of change, 2011 (Box 48, Folder 635)
  - Reflections on the Ford Foundation's Role in Building a Global Field of Development Finance and Economic Security, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 636)
  - Asset building - Miscellaneous reports, 2005-2011 (Box 48, Folder 637)
  - Hope credit union enterprise corporation - Overview and Strategic Directions, 2011 (Box 48, Folder 638)
  - Living Cities 2011 Annual Report (Box 48, Folder 639)
  - Finance and assets - Miscellaneous reports, 2007-2011 (Box 49, Folder 640-641)
  - Corporation for Enterprise Development (CFED) - Building Economic Security in America's Cities, 2011 (Box 49, Folder 642)
  - New York City Office of Financial Empowerment (OFE) October 2011 Advisory Council Meeting (Box 49, Folder 643)
  - Ford Foundation October 2011 Worldwide Leadership Meeting (Box 49, Folder 644)
  - ShoreBank, 2001-2008 (Box 49, Folder 645)
  - Ford Foundation Board of Trustees Asset Building and Community Development (ASSETS) Committee presentation, 2007 (Box 49, Folder 646)
  - Center for Economic Progress (CEP), 2007 (Box 49, Folder 647)
  - Oxfam - GROW Campaign, 2011 (Box 49, Folder 648)
  - Worldwatch Institute - Nourishing the Planet, 2011 (Box 49, Folder 649)
  - American Prospect - America's Endangered Middle Class, 2011 (Box 49, Folder 650)
  - Rainforest Alliance, 2010 (Box 49, Folder 651)
  - Vested for Growth (VFG), 2007-2010 (Box 50, Folder 652)
  - Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies - Explaining the Racial/Ethnic Wealth Gap, 2010 (Box 50, Folder 653)
  - RBI Master Circular on External Commercial Borrowings and Trade Credits, 2010 (Box 50, Folder 654)
  - New Yorker interview - Connie Bruck, 2004-2006 (Box 50, Folder 655)
  - Economic development - Miscellaneous readings and correspondence, 2002-2009 (Box 50, Folder 656-567)
  - Fannie Mae April 1990 Annual Housing Conference - Preserving Low-Income Housing Opportunities (Box 50, Folder 658-659)
  - Finance and assets - Meeting materials, part 1, 2006-2007 (Box 50, Folder 660)
  - Finance and assets - Meeting materials, part 2, 2007-2011 (Box 51, Folder 661-662)
  - Mortgage loans, livelihoods, and impact investment - Reports and meeting materials, 2007-2010 (Box 51, Folder 663-664)
  - Center for Responsible Lending (CRL) reports, 2008 (Box 51, Folder 665)
  - Agricultural development and livelihoods - Reports and meeting materials, 2007-2009 (Box 51, Folder 666-667)
  - Program Related Investments (PRI) May 2011 Mid-Year Loss Reserve Meeting (Box 51, Folder 668)
  - Building Economic Security Over a Lifetime (BESOL) May 2012 Grantee Convening, 2010-2012 (Box 52, Folder 669)
  - Hope Enterprise Corporation proposal, 2011 (Box 52, Folder 670)
  - Inequality seminar notes, undated (Box 52, Folder 671)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit initiatives - Monitoring and Evaluation, 2011 (Box 52, Folder 672)
  - Innovations for Poverty Action (IPA) Ultra Poor Graduation Pilots 2011 updates (Box 52, Folder 673)
  - ISEAL Alliance, 2011-2013 (Box 52, Folder 674)
  - ISEAL Alliance Phase 2 proposal, 2013 (Box 52, Folder 675)
  - Ford Foundation October 2013 presentation to Japanese Association of Charitable Organizations (JACO) (Box 52, Folder 676)
  - Investment Fund for African Agriculture (IIFFAA) August 2011 Investor Meeting, Luxembourg (Box 52, Folder 677-678)
  - Lincoln Center briefings - A Leap Forward for Dance, 2013-2014 (Box 52, Folder 679)
  - Living Cities July 2012 Executive Committee Meeting - Strategy (Box 52, Folder 680)
  - Mara Manus Program Officer Memo - Workforce Development, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 681)
  - Marketplace proposal, 2011 (Box 53, Folder 682)
  - Monitoring and Evaluation Working Group, 2012 (Box 53, Folder 683)
  - Migration seminar - Freedman Consulting, 2014 (Box 53, Folder 684)
  - Mara Manus Transition Memo - Workforce Development, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 685)
  - Initiative monitoring forms, 2011-2012 (Box 53, Folder 686)
  - Initiative monitoring forms, 2012 (Box 53, Folder 687)
  - Why an innovative anti-poverty program had no net impact - Jonathan Morduch, Shamika Ravi, and Jonathan Bauchet, 2011 (Box 53, Folder 688)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Natural Resources and Sustainable Development unit Fiscal Year 2011 Annual Report, 2010-2011 (Box 53, Folder 689)
  - Program Related Investments (PRI) Fund, 2007-2012 (Box 53, Folder 690)
  - Program Related Investments (PRI) consultant proposals, 2011-2013 (Box 53, Folder 691)
  - MART Knowledge Centre - Pro-poor Value Chain Development, undated (Box 53, Folder 692)
  - Rating Initiative (RI) Management Board/Donor Committee November 2011 Meeting (Box 53, Folder 693)
  - Root Capital - Financing Food Security and Nutrition, 2011 (Box 53, Folder 694)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) for Oklahoma Kids Research Advisory Council (RAC) January 2014 Meeting (Box 53, Folder 695)
  - Seal of Excellence for Poverty Outreach and Transformation in Microfinance, 2011 (Box 53, Folder 696)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) for Oklahoma Kids - Research Advisory Council (RAC) evaluation plan, 2011 (Box 54, Folder 697)
  - Breakthroughs in Shared Measurement and Social Impact - FSG Social Impact Advisors, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 698)
  - Social performance measurement proposals, 2012-2013 (Box 54, Folder 699)
  - Social Performance Task Force (SPTF), 2011 (Box 54, Folder 700)
  - Steve Homer - BIOSpartners, 2011 (Box 54, Folder 701)
  - SEEP Annual Conference, November 2012, Washington D.C. (Box 54, Folder 702)
  - University of North Carolina Center for Community Capital (CCC) - SaveNYC papers, circa 2012 (Box 54, Folder 703)
  - Yale University School of Management February 2012 Philanthropy Conference, 2011-2012 (Box 54, Folder 704)
  - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) Economic Development unit January 2000 Program Review, circa 2000 (Box 54, Folder 705)
  - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) Economic Development unit Statement of Purpose, 1996-1997 (Box 54, Folder 706)
  - Development finance thinking, 1996-1998 (Box 54, Folder 707)
  - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) Economic Development unit conceptual framework, undated (Box 54, Folder 708)